({
 "question": "Not having the abilities desired or necessary for any purpose",
 "options": ["Incompetent", "Impoverish", "Coxswain", "Devious"],
 "answer": "Incompetent",
 "category": 3
},
{
 "question": "Lizard that changes color in different situations",
 "options": ["Scruple", "Depredation", "Chameleon", "Whimsical"],
 "answer": "Chameleon",
 "category": 1
},
{
 "question": "Having the title of an office without the obligations",
 "options": ["Reciprocal", "Unsullied", "Titular", "Inflated"],
 "answer": "Titular",
 "category": 2
},
{
 "question": "An expression of disapproval or blame personally addressed to one censured",
 "options": ["Pitiful", "Reproof", "Mutation", "Raillery"],
 "answer": "Reproof",
 "category": 3
},
{
 "question": "To deliver an elaborate or formal public speech.",
 "options": ["Orate", "Magician", "Access", "Guzzle"],
 "answer": "Orate",
 "category": 2
},
{
 "question": "A wharf or artificial landing-place on the shore of a harbor or projecting into it",
 "options": ["Intolerable", "Quay", "Fez", "Insatiable"],
 "answer": "Quay",
 "category": 3
},
{
 "question": "Friendly counsel given by way of warning and implying caution or reproof",
 "options": ["Credence", "Colloquy", "Abyss", "Monition"],
 "answer": "Monition",
 "category": 1
},
{
 "question": "To make a beginning in some occupation or scheme",
 "options": ["Muster", "Embark", "Ocular", "Apprehensible"],
 "answer": "Ocular",
 "category": 2
},
{
 "question": "Able to reinforce sound by sympathetic vibrations",
 "options": ["Resonance", "Clandestine", "Diffusion", "Quietus"],
 "answer": "Resonance",
 "category": 3
},
{
 "question": "To send off or consign, as to an obscure position or remote destination",
 "options": ["Monolith", "Endurable", "Efficient", "Relegate"],
 "answer": "Relegate",
 "category": 1
})
